<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Algorithm Visualization</string>
    <string name="sort">SORT!</string>
    <string name="another">another</string>
    <string name="new_array">Generate New Array</string>
    <string name="selection">One of the simplest sorting algorithms works as follows: First, find the smallest item in the array and exchange it with the first entry
        (itself if the first entry is already the smallest). Then, find the next smallest item and exchange it with the second entry. Continue in this way until the entire
        array is sorted. This method is called selection sort because it works by repeatedly selecting the smallest remaining item.</string>
    <string name="insertion">Consider the cards one at a time, inserting each into its proper place among those already considered (keeping them sorted).
        In a computer implementation, we need to make space to insert the current item by moving larger items one position to the right,
        before inserting the current item into the vacated position. </string>
    <string name="bubble">Transfer the biggest number to the last position</string>
    <string name="shell">The idea is to rearrange the array to give it the property that taking every hth entry (starting anywhere) yields a sorted subsequence.
        Such an array is said to be h-sorted. Put another way, an h-sorted array is h independent sorted subsequences, interleaved together.
        By h-sorting for some large values of h, we can move items in the array long distances and thus make it easier to h-sort for smaller values of h.
        Using such a procedure for any sequence of values of h that ends in 1 will produce a sorted array . In this app , i use 3x+1 increment sequence:  1, 4, 13, 40, 121, 364, 1093, …
        or (3^k-1)/2 , not greater than N/3 .
    </string>
    <string name="merge">Combining 2 ordered arrays to make one larger ordered array. This operation immediately leads to a simple recursive sort method known as mergesort :
        to sort an array, divide it into two halves, sort the two halves (recursively), and then merge the results.</string>
    <string name="quick">Pick a pivot , split array to 2 sides of the pivot, bigger than and smaller than, do it recursively</string>
</resources>